me.
[Confidence: 98.40%]
Hi.
[Confidence: 76.70%]
I'm trying to relax.
[Confidence: 93.77%]
Would you mind?
[Confidence: 84.70%]
Oh, sorry, mister.
[Confidence: 81.67%]
Hey, kid. Kid, kid.
[Confidence: 88.42%]
Just come over here and sit down, would you?
[Confidence: 96.37%]
Okay.
[Confidence: 71.20%]
What's your name, mister? My name is Adam.
[Confidence: 98.90%]
You look like my grandpa except he's not as old.
[Confidence: 94.08%]
That's very...
[Confidence: 95.15%]
That's very rude.
[Confidence: 98.00%]
I'm Adam.
[Confidence: 99.90%]
Who are you?
[Confidence: 100.00%]
Joseph.
[Confidence: 96.70%]
Where's your mother?
[Confidence: 99.90%]
She's with her boyfriend.
[Confidence: 99.92%]
I'm supposed to wait over here.
[Confidence: 97.42%]
I'm eight and three quarters, mister.
[Confidence: 94.28%]
How old are you?
[Confidence: 100.00%]
Mister, you're boring.
[Confidence: 99.37%]
Hey, listen, kid.
[Confidence: 94.83%]
Hey listen I'd like some peace and quiet. Please?
[Confidence: 85.47%]
You're grumpy mister. Is that why that woman left you on the bench? Was she your girlfriend?
[Confidence: 92.51%]
No. No wasn't. Listen
[Confidence: 87.78%]
I have a girlfriend mister. And I'm only in the second grade. Where's your girlfriend?
[Confidence: 92.19%]
My wife, Elizabeth.
[Confidence: 96.77%]
gone.
[Confidence: 98.40%]
Well, where has she gone to?
[Confidence: 96.55%]
She's gone.
[Confidence: 100.00%]
Gone.
[Confidence: 99.70%]
Dead.
[Confidence: 99.20%]
Oh.
[Confidence: 100.00%]
That's sad.
Well, my girlfriend Katie,
[Confidence: 91.83%]
she's still really young.
[Confidence: 99.98%]
Was she a good girlfriend?
[Confidence: 99.26%]
Katie's the best I've had.
[Confidence: 97.88%]
Yes. Elizabeth was one of a kind.
[Confidence: 90.53%]
Why? Have you ever had any other girlfriends?
[Confidence: 96.75%]
Yesterday, I brought Katie a flower she gave me a kiss on the cheek.
[Confidence: 96.80%]
Have you ever brought a girl a flower?
[Confidence: 95.67%]
Kid, you've got a lot to learn about relationships.
[Confidence: 95.49%]
Have you ever looked into someone's eyes and had a whole...
[Confidence: 96.20%]
a whole conversation in an instant.
[Confidence: 98.93%]
Laughed with someone.
[Confidence: 99.53%]
Kept laughing until you even forgot why you were laughing.
[Confidence: 97.67%]
Have you ever cried when...
[Confidence: 95.30%]
I cried last night when I said goodbye to Katie.
[Confidence: 99.27%]
But that was because I had scraped my knee badly.
[Confidence: 97.69%]
Yes?
[Confidence: 57.90%]
Are you going to get a new girlfriend?
[Confidence: 97.12%]
going to get a new girlfriend for all those things?
[Confidence: 94.95%]
Nah.
[Confidence: 54.20%]
I'm happy just by myself.
[Confidence: 96.96%]
I think you're grumpy.
[Confidence: 99.25%]
I have lots of girlfriends, mister.
[Confidence: 96.05%]
Over six.
[Confidence: 95.60%]
Lizzie was my one and only.
[Confidence: 95.03%]
Ugh.
[Confidence: 62.60%]
You talk about your girlfriend a lot.
[Confidence: 99.06%]
My wife.
[Confidence: 86.60%]
I love getting girlfriends, mister. You should try it.
[Confidence: 93.63%]
there's not enough time left for me for those kind of shenanigans.
[Confidence: 92.68%]
Plus, I thought I was a boring, grumpy old guy.
[Confidence: 95.98%]
Nah, you're nice.
[Confidence: 89.00%]
Well, once you stop reading.
[Confidence: 88.78%]
See that pretty girl over there?
[Confidence: 99.52%]
I'm about to get a new girlfriend in ten seconds.
[Confidence: 92.17%]
There's always time.
[Confidence: 95.43%]
Gotta go, mister. Bye.
[Confidence: 87.75%]
Nice day, isn't it?
[Confidence: 97.88%]
Yeah.
[Confidence: 96.90%]
It's beautiful.
[Confidence: 88.05%]
I really enjoy the park.
[Confidence: 91.42%]