Hey guys, what's up? It's and welcome to a brand new video.
[Confidence: 92.34%]
So you guys seem to love my language series so today I decided that I wanted to try to speak Dutch.
[Confidence: 95.26%]
Keep in mind that I've never heard this language before so you should probably be prepared for bad Dutch.
[Confidence: 96.10%]
Anyway, without further ado, let's get started.
[Confidence: 98.44%]
Hello!
[Confidence: 90.70%]
one was easy.
[Confidence: 99.57%]
Good morning!
[Confidence: 98.50%]
My name is Sunny in this case my name is Scott.
[Confidence: 95.59%]
My name is Scott.
[Confidence: 95.62%]
My name is Sunny.
[Confidence: 92.10%]
Over to the next one which is...
[Confidence: 86.59%]
next one which is thank you
[Confidence: 78.75%]
Do you speak English?
[Confidence: 92.10%]
engels
[Confidence: 65.30%]
Dammit, I can't concentrate
[Confidence: 83.78%]
One more time
[Confidence: 91.40%]
Spreek je engels
[Confidence: 97.33%]
I'm just gonna go over to the numbers
[Confidence: 93.70%]
[Confidence: 76.10%]
3 4 5
[Confidence: 84.50%]
5 6
[Confidence: 92.95%]
7 8
[Confidence: 82.40%]
8 9
[Confidence: 93.70%]
[Confidence: 62.60%]
category
[Confidence: 97.00%]
Boat
[Confidence: 83.80%]
Bus
[Confidence: 99.30%]
Train
[Confidence: 87.00%]
Ticket
[Confidence: 90.70%]
Hospital
[Confidence: 94.80%]
Today
[Confidence: 99.50%]
Tomorrow
[Confidence: 90.20%]
Yesterday
[Confidence: 81.30%]
really hard to say, holy shit
[Confidence: 95.33%]
shit what about now?
[Confidence: 91.83%]
I'm from Australia
[Confidence: 91.33%]
I'm from Norway would probably be like
[Confidence: 89.50%]
I'm from Norway
[Confidence: 81.03%]
or I don't know what Norway is in Dutch
[Confidence: 90.03%]
but yeah
[Confidence: 83.40%]
Prost
[Confidence: 56.40%]
Please speak more slowly
[Confidence: 94.23%]
Please, can you speak little bit
[Confidence: 68.92%]
Oh my god that is almost the same as in German just harder the heck
[Confidence: 80.05%]
so first of all the first word is impossible to pronounce it's like
[Confidence: 93.72%]
pronounce it. It's like
[Confidence: 82.53%]
Okay, I have to listen it one more time
[Confidence: 89.93%]
ashtublieft
[Confidence: 80.00%]
Ashtublieft
[Confidence: 92.90%]
langsame...
[Confidence: 86.40%]
I will not end this video until I can say that.
[Confidence: 89.83%]
Ashtublieft
[Confidence: 99.00%]
Kan tu wat langsamer
[Confidence: 85.08%]
Ashtublieft
[Confidence: 99.50%]
Kan tu wat langsamer spreken?
[Confidence: 95.86%]
To be honest, it sounds like Danish. Like the accent
[Confidence: 89.76%]
sounds Danish. Ashtublieft
[Confidence: 90.20%]
Kan tu langsamer spreken?
[Confidence: 91.90%]
Freaking nail
[Confidence: 70.40%]
In case you wondered, I was happy about that one.
[Confidence: 96.87%]
about that one. And to end this video, I'm gonna say goodbye.
[Confidence: 88.64%]
dag! Alright, so thank you so much for watching this video. If you liked it,
[Confidence: 85.99%]
make sure to give it a big thumbs up I'll see you guys in two or three days
[Confidence: 90.78%]
with a brand new video. I promise. I promise. Anyway, again, thanks for
[Confidence: 90.77%]
watching. I love you guys and peace, bye!
[Confidence: 86.94%]