In the world of magic, everything that disappears reappears.
[Confidence: 87.39%]
It is very good to be back!
[Confidence: 95.54%]
Come up! You're gonna be our helper!
[Confidence: 79.93%]
Okay, disappear in three, two, one.
[Confidence: 86.08%]
Daniel Atlas the wants to see a magic
[Confidence: 97.70%]
think we would have made the horse proud Atlas was on.
[Confidence: 86.32%]
Really? I'll be the judge of that.
[Confidence: 93.83%]
According to that card for some reason, I need you.
[Confidence: 94.18%]
Why not the other horsemen? other horsemen are dead.
[Confidence: 91.98%]
Oh my God, what?
[Confidence: 77.83%]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. dead to me.
[Confidence: 80.92%]
Things got too real for them to give up, stuff directing.
[Confidence: 81.78%]
I'm talking about a trick that is bigger and better than anything you have ever seen.
[Confidence: 95.63%]
But it's now or never. What's the trick?
[Confidence: 89.55%]
A heart diamond, valuable jewel in history.
[Confidence: 82.30%]
what makes this diamond so special?
[Confidence: 96.87%]
You can magical tarot card told us.
[Confidence: 84.20%]
For decades, the have been selling diamonds to warlords,
[Confidence: 90.96%]
dealers traffickers to help their money.
[Confidence: 95.77%]
If you want to stop the devil, don't cut off her hands. You her wallet.
[Confidence: 84.09%]
Open sesame.
[Confidence: 77.80%]
Still safe with me.
[Confidence: 85.58%]
Relax, diamonds.
[Confidence: 91.55%]
forever. him!
[Confidence: 84.55%]
Jack, what are you doing here? in your ass.
[Confidence: 97.52%]
we reach?
[Confidence: 86.50%]
later.
[Confidence: 96.40%]
Hi guys.
[Confidence: 82.90%]
don't know you.
[Confidence: 80.43%]
Let's go!
[Confidence: 94.95%]
My horsemen.
[Confidence: 97.85%]
We're brought together for a reason.
[Confidence: 91.25%]
we kick in?
[Confidence: 84.67%]
Bring down two generations of criminals with a single slide of hand.
[Confidence: 89.18%]
Eight magicians against worldwide criminal network.
[Confidence: 87.13%]
I like our chances.
[Confidence: 93.73%]
to see a magic trick.
[Confidence: 94.34%]
That is.
[Confidence: 73.80%]
You join the show?
[Confidence: 71.15%]
we get on with it.
[Confidence: 83.98%]
guys, dead ends.
[Confidence: 84.80%]
Open sesame.
[Confidence: 91.50%]
a
[Confidence: 62.90%]
With the try.
[Confidence: 56.43%]
Was it?
[Confidence: 77.95%]
Never know.
[Confidence: 78.35%]
I think you do know.
[Confidence: 98.34%]