As the stealth bombers rolled off the assembly line,
[Confidence: 99.21%]
rumors surfaced that the military was test-flying recovered alien craft
[Confidence: 97.59%]
at a secret government base known as Area 51.
[Confidence: 99.98%]
If the military was going to test-fly alien craft,
[Confidence: 99.94%]
Area 51 was the perfect place to do it.
[Confidence: 100.00%]
Located some 125 miles outside of Las Vegas,
it is one of the least populated expanses in the United States.
[Confidence: 99.93%]
Area 51 is surrounded on three sides by military testing grounds
[Confidence: 98.40%]
and hidden from public view behind the Groom Mountain Range.
[Confidence: 99.37%]
This Russian satellite photo shows the base as it appeared in the 1960s.
[Confidence: 99.95%]